Guide to the UNITE HERE! Local 8 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- HOTEL, MOTEL AND RESTAURANT EMPLOYEES LOCAL 61, TACOMA, 1901-1979; SUBGROUP 9 (Box-folder 18/1-22, 19/1-20, 19/36, 20/2-21/2, 22/1-26/10, 26/15, 34/6-10)
  - MINUTES, 1902-1979; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 18/7-8, 19/1-20, 19/36, 20/2-21/2, 34/6-10)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1958 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1959 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1961 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1966 (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 19/20)
    - Minutes of special meetings on negotiations, 1960 (Box-folder 19/36)
  - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, 1931-1979; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 18/9-11)
    - Secret ballot on dues increase, 1979 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Local 61 photograph album, 1931-1950 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Photographs, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - MEMBERSHIP RECORDS, 1901-1953; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 18/12-14, 22/1-25/9)
    - Dues ledger, 1901 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Dues ledger, 1901-1902 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Dues ledger, 1902 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Dues ledger, 1903 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Dues ledger, 1904 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Dues ledger, 1905 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Dues ledger, 1906 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Dues ledger, 1907 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Dues ledger, 1908 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Dues ledger, 1909 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Dues ledger, 1910 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Dues ledger, 1911 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Dues ledger, 1912 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Dues ledger, 1913 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Dues ledger, 1914 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Dues ledger, 1915 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Dues ledger, 1916 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Dues ledger, 1918 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Dues ledger, 1919 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Dues ledger, 1922 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Dues ledger, 1923 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Dues ledger, 1924 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Dues ledger, 1925 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Dues ledger, 1926 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Dues ledger, 1927 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Dues ledger, 1928 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - Dues ledger, 1929 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Dues ledger, 1930 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Dues ledger, 1931 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Dues ledger, 1932 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Dues ledger, 1933 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Dues ledger, 1934 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Dues ledger, 1935 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Dues ledger, 1936 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Dues ledger, 1937 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Dues ledger H-L, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 25/6)
      Privacy: includes SSN
    - Reinstatement ledger, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Reinstatement ledger, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Reinstatement ledger, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Trial transcript, James Canto, 1942 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Trial transcript, Fred Wheeler, 1950 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Trial records, Florence Teska, 1951 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1966-1972; SERIES 4 (Box-folder 18/15-16)
    - Member correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 18/15)
    - Member correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1901-1969; SERIES 5 (Box-folder 26/1-10, 26/15)
    - Cash book, 1901-1938 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Cash book, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Cash book, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Disbursement ledger, 1941-1953 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Business agent daily receipts record, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Business agent daily receipts record, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Business agent daily receipts record, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - Business agent daily receipts record, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Ledger of checks received from houses and given to members, 1945-1967 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Permit record, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Savings account books, 1949-1969 (Box-folder 26/15)
  - COLLECTIVE BARGAINING RECORDS, 1917-1970; SERIES 6 (Box-folder 18/17-22)
    - Knox, Inc. contract, 1917 (Box-folder 18/17)
    - Wage scale & working rules, 1948-1957 (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Standard contract and agreement, Local 61 and Local 711, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Contracts and negotiations, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Tacoma contract negotiations and strike, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Local 711 contract, 1962 (Box-folder 18/22)
- LOCAL 20, TACOMA, 1977-1983; SUBGROUP 10 (Box-folder 11/13, 18/23-26)
  - Membership meeting minutes, 1981 (Box-folder 18/23)
  - Insurance policy, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Working agreement and wage scale, 1977 (Box-folder 18/25)
  - C.I. Shenanigans organizing, 1983 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Payroll ledger, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 18/26)
- HOTEL AND RESTAURANT EMPLOYEES AND BARTENDERS LOCAL 791, ABERDEEN, 1994-2007; SUBGROUP 11 (Box-folder 19/21, 26/11)
  - Minutes, 1994-2007 (Box-folder 26/11)
  - Wage scale and trade regulations, Local 791, Aberdeen, 1977 (Box-folder 19/21)
- CULINARY AND BEVERAGE WORKERS UNION LOCAL 529, BELLINGHAM, 1927-1971; SUBGROUP 12 (Box-folder 26/12-14, 28/3)
  - Dues ledger (A-G), 1927-1930 (Box-folder 26/12)
  - Dues ledger (H-N), 1927-1930 (Box-folder 26/13)
  - Dues ledger (O-Z), 1927-1930 (Box-folder 26/14)
  - Agreements, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 28/3)
- CULINARY WORKERS AND BARTENDERS UNION LOCAL 451, EVERETT, 1935-1938; SUBGROUP 13 (Box-folder 27/1-5, 28/2, 33/10, 33/12, 37/1)
  - Meeting attendance log, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Dues ledger, 1988 (Box-folder 33/10)
  - Mt. Vernon dues ledger, 1938 (Box-folder 33/12)
  - Cash book, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Snohomish County Beneficial Association bylaws, 1973 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Contract and agreement pamphlets, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Contracts (part 1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Contracts (part 2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Contracts, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Health Trust Fund eligibility report, form 19M, 1988-1989; diazo microfiche (Box-folder 28/2)
- COOKS AND WAITERS CULINARY ALLIANCE LOCAL 730, BREMERTON, 1915-1980; 1947-1980; SUBGROUP 14 (Box-folder 18/27-29, 26/16-17, 27/6)
  - Meeting minutes, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Dues ledger A-D, 1947-1980 (Box-folder 18/28)
  - Dues ledger E-J, 1947-1980 (Box-folder 18/29)
  - Dues ledger K-P, 1947-1980 (Box-folder 26/16)
  - Dues ledger R-Z, 1947-1980 (Box-folder 26/17)
  - Minimum wage scale, 1915 (Box-folder 27/6)
- CULINARY WORKERS AND BARTENDERS LOCAL 596, RENTON, 1947-1975; SUBGROUP 15 (Box-folder 28/3, 31/7-9)
  - MINUTES, 1947-1960; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 31/7-8)
    - Meeting minutes, 1948-1960; 1 reel 16 mm diazo microfilm (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Executive Board minutes, 1947-1960; 1 reel 16 mm diazo microfilm; portions filmed out-of-order (Box-folder 31/8)
  - MEMBERSHIP RECORDS, 1958-1975; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 28/3, 31/9)
    - Dues ledger, 1958-1971; 4 reels of 16 mm diazo microfilm (Box-folder 31/9)
    - Dues ledger, 1958-1975; diazo microfiche (Box-folder 28/3)
- LOCAL 61 BUILDING CORPORATION, 1945-1976; SUBGROUP 16 (Box-folder 32/1-15, 37/3)
  - Records, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 32/1)
  - Records, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 32/2)
  - Records, 1948 (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Records, 1949 (Box-folder 32/4)
  - Records, 1950 (Box-folder 32/5)
  - Records, 1951 (Box-folder 32/6)
  - Records, 1952 (Box-folder 32/7)
  - Records, 1953 (Box-folder 32/8)
  - Records, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 32/9)
  - Records, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 32/10)
  - Records, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 32/11)
  - Records, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 32/12)
  - Records, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 32/13)
  - Records, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 32/14)
  - Records, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 32/15)
  - Records, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 37/3)